Leave or life?
المغادرة أم الحياة؟
Life.
الحياة
What's going on?!
ماذا يحصل؟
They've multiplied and are barking like animals!
لقد تضاعفوا، والآن ينبحون كالحيوانات
What happened to you guys?!
ماذا حصل لكم يا رفاق؟
Aren't any of you real?!
هل أي منكم حقيقي؟
Hey, Sanji!
!مهلًا يا سانجي
Pudding! Chopper!
بودينغ، تشوبر
Carrot!
كاروت
Nami!
نامي
Untie me!
فُك قيدي
She's talking like a human!
إنها تتحدث كالبشر
I'm the real one!
أنا الحقيقية
Listen up! I was looking for you!
اسمع، كنت أبحث عنك
Why did you just grab me like that?!
كيف تجرؤ على تقييدي هكذا فجأةً؟
I... I'm really... really sorry...
أعتذر بشدة
But this is pretty crazy. What's going on?
لكن هذا مفاجئ بالتأكيد ماذا يحصل؟
This one certainly looks like me.
إنها تشبهني تمامًا بالتأكيد
This would be easy if the real ones were all among them.
إن كان جميع الحقيقيين من بينهم هذا سيجعل الأمر سهلًا
Well, you guys were the ones who multiplied!
ظننتكم تضاعفتم
We can't multiply! I mean, we did, but...
لم نتضاعف، رغم أن هذا ما يبدو عليه الأمر
Hey, you!
اسمع يا هذا
You know what happened, don't you?
تعلم شيئًا، أليس كذلك؟
You were here the whole time, even when we were attacked by that woman!
لقد كنت هنا طوال الوقت حتى عندما هاجمَتنا تلك المرأة
I didn't see anything!
لم أرَ شيئًا
Hey, what happened?
مهلًا، ما الذي حدث؟
I was attacked by you, Luffy!
أنت هاجمتَني يا لوفي
By me?!
أنا؟
Technically, it wasn't you. But it was a fake that we tried to escape with!
لأكون دقيقة، المزيف الذي ظننته أنت وحاولت الهرب معه
Huh? What do you mean?
ماذا تعنين؟
Then, that "Luffy" suddenly turned into a giant woman... and attacked us...
لوفي ذاك تحول فجأةً إلى امرأة عملاقة وهاجمَتنا
Let go of me!
اتركيني
Who are you?!
من أنتِ-تيا؟
I'm Brûlée!
أنا بروليه
Brûlée?
بروليه؟
A cute rabbit and a pretty girl... How nice...
أرنبة ظريفة وفتاة جميلة كم هذا لطيف
When I see those beautiful faces,
عندما أرى هذه الوجوه الجميلة
it makes me want to scratch them up!
!أرغب بشقها
Nami!
نامي
No!
كلّا
W-Where's Luffy?!
أ-أين لوفي؟
"Where," indeed.
أينه يا ترى؟
He's probably wandering, lost in the forest.
أظنه هائمًا في الغابة
Clima-Tact!
كليما تاكت
Nami, are you okay?!
نامي، هل أنتِ بخير؟
Yeah! That was close!
أجل، كان ذلك وشيكًا
Thank you, Usopp!
شكرًا لك يا أوسوب
You cheeky little...
يا لوقاحتك
Carrot!
كاروت
Leave it to me!
اتركي الأمر لي
Eleclaw!
إيليكلو
It's my turn!
حان دوري
Reflection!
ريفليكشن
Carrot!
كاروت
Are you okay?!
هل أنتِ بخير؟
Carrot's punch came out of the mirror!
خرجت لكمة كاروت من المرآة
I'm a mirror!
أنا مرآة
I ate the Mirror-Mirror Fruit and became a mirror human!
أكلتُ فاكهة المرآة وأصبحتُ مرآةً بشرية
Just like a mirror reflects light, if you throw a punch at my mirror,
كما تعكس المرآة الضوء، إن سدّدتِ لكمةً على مرآتي
it will also reflect it back!
ستردها معكوسةً لك
Be careful, Carrot!
احذري يا كاروت
I'll break your stupid mirror!
سأدمر مرآتك الغبية
Mirro-world!
ميرور وورلد
Carrot!
كاروت
What did you do to her?!
ماذا فعلت بها؟
That's the first!
انتهيت من واحد
I can't get out! Let me out!
لا يمكنني الخروج، أخرجيني
What did you do?! Let Carrot go!
ماذا فعلت؟ أعيديها لنا
Stay away, Nami!
ابقي بعيدة يا نامي
I can't do that.
لا يمكنني فعل هذا
Ah! Nami!
نامي
Chopper!
تشوبر
Help me!
ساعداني
Mama already knows that you guys are here!
عرفَت ماما بأنكم كنتم هنا منذ زمن
Did you think no one knew?! How idiotic!
هل ظننتم أننا لن نلاحظ ذلك؟ يا للغباء
We're all coming after you now. Mama ordered us to!
نحن نهاجمكم جميعًا وفقًا لأوامر ماما
That one...
هذا
And them...
وهؤلاء
Those fools...
وأولئك الحمقى
And him!
وهو كذلك
We've all been told by Mama that we need to...
أمرتنا ماما جميعًا قائلة
"let the Straw Hats keep going for now. Just don't let them find Sanji.
«مهّلوا طاقم قبعة القش رويدًا، لكن لا تسمحوا لهم برؤية سانجي»
Make them regret trying to mess with me!"
«اجعلوهم يندمون على الوقوف ضدي»
Mama knows everything!
تعلم ماما كل شيء
Alright, homies! Don't let them escape!
والآن يا هوميز، لا تسمحوا لهما بالهرب
You can't get away!
لن تهربا من هنا
No!
كلا
Chopper!
تشوبر
Nami, run!
اهربي يا نامي
There are too many of them! If all three of us get caught, we're done for!
هنالك عدد كبير من الأعداء، سنموت إن أمسكوا بثلاثتنا جميعًا
They're members of an emperor's crew! We underestimated them!
،إنهم أفراد من طاقم إمبراطورة كان علينا أن نكون أكثر حذرًا
Go look for Luffy! I'll do the best I can here!
ابحثي عن لوفي، سأصدهم قدر استطاعتي
Okay! I'll be back!
حسنًا، سأعود حتمًا
Rumble!
رامبل
Monster Point!
مونستر بوينت
Look at that! You were already interesting, but you're able to do this too?!
،هذا مدهش، إنه في الأصل حيوان عجيب ومع هذا يملك أيضًا مهارةً مميزة كهذه
Mama will be happy!
ستكون ماما سعيدة
She doesn't just seek every race; she also collects all kinds of strange creatures.
جميع الأجناس ليست كافية بالنسبة لها، لأنها جامعة حيوانات لا نظيرَ لها في العالم
Now, catch them!
هيا، اقبضوا عليهما
Stop, you brat!
توقفي أيتها الشقية
Go away!
ابتعدي
Luffy! Where are you?!
أين أنت يا لوفي؟
Then, I kept running around,
وبعدها، واصلت الهرب منهم
looking for you until it got dark.
وكنت أبحث عنك حتى حل الظلام
I see! I'm glad that you found me!
فهمت، عثرتي عليّ في وقته
All right!
حسنًا
Let's go save Chopper and Carrot right now! Where are they?!
،لنذهب الآن لإنقاذ تشوبر وكاروت أين هما؟
Right here.
هنا
All of that happened right here.
كل ما قصصته عليك حصل هنا
But now, they're all gone. That's why I'm asking this guy!
لكنهم اختفيا الآن، لهذا أسأل ذلك الرجل
You were watching the whole time! Where's Chopper? And what about Carrot?!
كنتَ هنا طوال الوقت، أين تشوبر؟ وكاروت؟
That Brûlée lady and the forest monsters didn't mess with you at all!
تلك المرأة بروليه ووحوش الغابة لم يتعرضوا لك بأذى
That means you're one of them!
هذا يعني أنك رفيقهم
Uh... One of them? Well, we're not enemies...
رفيقهم؟ لستُ عدوًّا لهم بالتأكيد
Oh! If you want to know, bring me some apple juice from over on my left–
إن كنتِ تريدينني أن أخبركِ، فأحضري لي بعضًا من عصير التفاح الموجود على يساري
We don't have time for that!
ليس لدينا وقت لهذا
If you tell us something useful, then sure, we'll bring it to you!
إن أخبرتنا شيئًا مفيدًا حقًّا، سأحضره لك
Really?!
أتعني ذلك حقًّا؟
Yeah, since you've been mentioning it so much, I wanna try it too.
نعم، إصرارك على هذا أرغبني في شربه أيضًا
By the way,
بالمناسبة
you look pretty strong, but...
أنت تبدو قويًا جدًا
are you ?
هل أنتِ قوية أيضًا؟
Y-Yes, I am strong! Why does that matter?
نـ-نعم، أنا قوية، لمَ تسأل؟
I see. Appearances aren't everything, I guess.
هكذا! مظهرك لا يدل على هذا
That reindeer guy was surprisingly strong,
غزال الرنة ذاك كان قويًا بشكل مفاجئ
but the trees of the forest attacked him without hesitation.
ولكن أشجار الغابة هاجموه بلا تردد
Once they get an order, they don't stop
عندما يؤمرون بشيء، فلن يتوقفوا
until they complete it!
حتى ينجزوا مهمتهم
Really? Then, why did they stop attacking me?
إذًا، لمَ توقفوا عن مهاجمتي؟
When I beat a bunch of them, they left me alone, too!
هدأوا بعد أن ضربتُ عددًا كبيرًا منهم
Hey, how are they alive, anyways?
وبالمناسبة، كيف يمكنهم التحرك؟
Every six months, each resident of Totto Land
...يتوجب على مواطنو توتولاند كل ستة أشهر
must pay a month's worth of their soul to the kingdom,
...دفع ضريبة للبلاد مقدارها شهر من أرواحهم...
in exchange for their safety.
من أجل ضمان سلامتهم...
Soul?
أرواحهم؟
Yeah, their lifespan, basically.
بلى، هذا ينتقص من حياتهم
So the people lose two months of their lifespan in a year...
إذ يخسر الأشخاص شهرين من دورة حياتهم في العام الواحد
and one year of their lifespan for every six.
وعامًا من دورة حياتهم كل 6 أعوام
How is that possible?
ماذا تعني؟
Linlin, I mean, Big Mom ate the Soul-Soul Fruit.
لينلين، أعني بيغ مام أكلت فاكهة الروح
She can manipulate people's souls.
فبات بإمكانها التلاعب بأرواح البشر
With that power, she takes the life span of her citizens.
تأخذ جزءًا من دورة حياة المواطنين بتلك القوة
At that moment, the citizens have to choose to stay in Totto Land or leave.
وفي تلك اللحظة، يجب عليهم أن يختاروا البقاء في توتولاند أو المغادرة
And by spreading the collected souls all over the country,
وبنشر الأرواح التي جُمِعت في جميع أرجاء الدولة
all kinds of things take on a life of their own.
تدب الحياة في شتى الأشياء ويصبحون أشبه بالبشر
We call those who came to life "the homies."
ندعو من تدبُّ فيهم الحياة بالهوميز
The collection and distribution of souls
...والتجسيدات التي صُنعت من روح لينلين أقصد بيغ مام نفسها، تجمع وتوزع الأرواح
That's what happens in Totto Land.
هذه حقيقة توتولاند
When we first arrived, there were lots of odd things alive in the town of chocolate.
حين كنا في بلدة الشوكولاتة سابقًا رأينا مختلف الأشياء على قيد الحياة
Is that why the crocodile was able to talk?! And the human-like rabbit?!
ألهذا تحدث التمساح وتصرف الأرنب كالبشر؟
Yeah, that's right. Animals can be personified too.
كلامك سليم، يمكن للحيوانات أن تصبح شبيهةً بالبشر أيضًا
What an incredible ability!
يا لها من قوة
So, what about these guys?
وماذا هؤلاء؟
They're something else.
حالهم يختلف
Brûlée used her ability to turn normal animals into people.
إنهم مجرد حيوانات حولتهم بروليه بقوتها إلى أشكال بشرية
Oh, by the way, souls can't be put into other people or corpses.
بالمناسبة، لا يمكن غرس الأرواح داخل بشر آخرين أو جثث
Why didn't you tell me that before?! You've been watching me the whole time!
لماذا لم تقل شيئًا؟ لقد كنت تشاهدنا طوال الوقت
Because I didn't want to get involved!
لأنني لم أُرِد أن أتورط في أي شيء
If you didn't want to get involved, then why are you buried here?!
لماذا أنت مدفون هنا إن لم ترغب بالتورط بالأمر؟
Why?! Who are you?!
لماذا؟ من أنت؟
Tell me! I'll get you the juice!
أخبرني وسأمنحك العصير
O-Okay! I'll tell you! Just get off of me! Stop!
فـ- فهمت، اتركني لأخبرك، انزل عني
Long ago... very long ago, I was Big Mom's... I mean, the pirate Charlotte Linlin's...
...قبل زمنٍ، كنت لبيغ مام القرصانة شارلوت لينلين
Linlin's...
...للينلين
Linlin's husband!
لـ لينلين زوجًا...
W-Why is one of the Three Sweet Commanders here?!
لـ-لماذا أحد جنرالات الحلوى الثلاثة هنا؟
Straw Hat!
يا قبعة القش
I'm going to...
سأضع
put an end...
نهايةً
to your life!
لحياتكم
Big Mom's...
زوج بيغ مام
...ex-husband?!
السابق؟
She and I had two daughters, and then she threw me out.
هجرتني حالما أنجبت مني ابنتين
It's not that anyone's after me...
إنهم لا يتفادون مهاجمتي
They just don't pay attention to me!
إنهم لا يهتمون لأمري فقط
Who's that?
من هذا؟
S-Sir, what brings you here?
سـ- سيدي، ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Am I not allowed to be here?
ألا يُسمح بوجودي هنا؟
No! Of course you are.
كلا بالتأكيد، أنت مرحّب بك
– His body's coming out! – Get back, Nami!
جسده يخرج- تراجعي يا نامي-
No!
كلا
We thought he was a giant!
ظننته كان عملاقًا
What's wrong with you? What kind of a fool just gives the enemy information like that?!
أمجنون أنت؟ كيف لك أن تفشي المعلومات للعدو هكذا أيها الأحمق؟
W-Wait, Cracker-kun !
ا-انتظر يا كراكر-كن
I want to see my daughter, Chiffon, even if only for a moment!
أرغب برؤية ابنتي شيفون حتى ولو للحظة فقط
I heard she got married! I want to congratulate her!
سمعتُ بأنها تزوجت، أريد أن أبارك لها
That's why I need you to let me talk to Linlin!
لذا دعني أتحدث إلى لينلين
Also, I heard that Lola ran away!
وسمعتُ بأن لولا هربت
They're both my precious daughters!
كلتاهن ابنتاي العزيزتان
Lola?
لولا؟
Ran away?
هربت؟
One of my beloved older sisters
إحدى أخواتي الكبيرات التي أحببتها بشدّة خرجت إلى البحر بحثًا عن الحبّ
To seek a match of her own.
وبحثًا عن الزواج
Lola... ran away from home?
لولا التي هربت من منزلها؟
Cracker-kun, let go of me! I just want to see Lola... and Chiffon...
كراكر-كن، أفلتني لا أريد سوى أن أرى لولا وشيفون
I just want to see my daughters!
أريد أن أرى ابنتاي فقط
Lola... That Lola... Could it be?
...لولا، هل يعقل أن لولا
Lola, you guys went to the New World?!
لولا، أذهبتم إلى العالم الجديد؟
We didn't go there! We were born in the New World!
لم نذهب إلى العالم الجديد، بل وُلدنا فيه
Mama is a pirate, too. Ah...
...أمي قرصانة و
that's right...
تفضلي شيئاً لك
This is Mama's vivre card. I'll let you have it.
،إنها الفيفر كارد الخاصة بأمي سأعطيه لك
Paper?
ورقة؟
Wow! How lucky! Captain Lola's mama is a great pirate!
مذهل، أنتِ محظوظة والدة القائدة لولا قرصانة عظيمة
Take good care of it! It'll definitely be useful one day!
لا تفقديها أنا واثق أنها ستفيدكِ يومًا ما
Everything's starting to make sense...
توضح كل شيء الآن
In that case, could... Lola's mama be...
...إذًا يا ترى، هل يعقل أن والدة لولا هي
Big Mom?!
بيغ مام؟
And this man is...
...وهذا الرجل هو
Lola's father?!
والد لولا؟
They're back! It's the rabbit and the crane!
عاد ذلك الأرنب مرة أخرى إلى هنا
They're... flying!
يمكنه الطيران؟
Stop! Randolph!
توقف يا راندولف
Was that haki?! No, not quite...
هاكي! ليس كذلك
What was it then?!
ماذا كان إذًا؟
They screamed...
لقد صرخوا
and withered up out of fear?!
وذبلوا من الخوف؟
You must think you're a big shot... if you think you're able to get in my way.
أتجرؤ على الوقوف في طريقي؟ متى أصبحت بهذه الجرأة؟
Randolph!
يا راندولف
I'm sorry. That was his idea.
أعتذر، كانت هذه فكرته
Liar! It was yours!
لا تكذب، بل كانت فكرتك أنت
They can talk!
تحدثا
We are very sorry.
نعتذر بشدة
Is he someone special?
هل هو شخص رفيع المستوى؟
He looks strong, that's for sure.
من الواضح أنه قوي
Mama always has her next move set in motion.
تبدأ ماما الهجوم أولًا
Since Straw Hat Luffy defeated Doflamingo,
بما أن قبعة القش لوفي هزم دوفلامينغو
she knew Brûlée would have trouble, so she sent me.
توقعَت أن تعاني بروليه من وقت عصيب، فأرسلَتني
I can't just let you say that, Big Brother!
لا يمكنني أن أسمح لك بقول هذا ببساطة يا أخي الكبير
Whoa! A tree monster!
ماذا؟ شجرة متوحشة؟
Oh, that woman!
...تلك المرأة
If she ordered me to do it,
إن طُلِب مني قتلهم، سأفعل هذا بالحال
That's right!
هذا صحيح-جو
We members of the Seducing Woods team
نحن فريق غابة الإغواء
have never allowed a single target of ours to leave alive!
لم نترك أي هدف يخرج من هنا على قيد الحياة قط-جو
Oh! It's not just Minister Cracker and Madame Brûlée...
ليس كراكر-ساما وبروليه-ساما فقط وإنما الملك كينغبوم-ساما هنا أيضًا
I can't believe all three of them are here at the same time!
يا للهول، جميعهم اجتمعوا هنا
That's nice and all, but we can't waste any time.
هذا عظيم، لكننا لا نملك الوقت لهدره الآن
By the midday tomorrow,
عند حلول ظهر الغد
the Vinsmoke siblings will arrive at Whole Cake Chateau.
جميع إخوة وأخوات عائلة فينسموك سيجتمعون ويدخلون قصر الكعكة الكاملة
Forming a family connection with the Vinsmokes is something that Mama has wanted for a long time.
تكوين روابط عائلية بعائلة فينسموك شيء تنتظره ماما بلهفة
We'll have Germa 66's formidable military and advanced technology.
يمكننا مشاركة جيرما 66 بجيشهم القوي وتقنيتهم العلمية
I know that!
أعلم هذا
They've turned into animals!
تحولوا إلى حيوانات
And... why is that branch talking?!
وكيف يمكن لفرع الشجرة ذاك أن يتحدث؟
I'm not a branch!
لستُ فرع شجرة
Look at this, Straw Hat!
انظر إلى هذا يا قبعة القش
Oh, Luffy!
لوفي
Luffy, Nami! Help!
يا لوفي ونامي، ساعدانا
Chopper got caught, too?!
قبضوا على تشوبر؟
What happened to you guys?! What are you doing in there?!
ماذا حصل أيها الرفاق؟ كيف دخلتما إلى هناك؟
She trapped us in the mirror! She has a mirror ability! Be careful!
احتجزَتنا في عالم المرآة إنها تملك قدرةً تتعلق بالمرايا فاحذرا
How's this, Brother Cracker?!
أرأيتَ ما أنجزتُ يا أخي كراكر؟
I've already got these fools...
أمسكت بهذين الغبيين
by the scruffs of their necks!
من مؤخرة عنقيهما
Hey, Chopper! Carrot! Are you okay?!
يا تشوبر وكاروت، هل أنتما بخير؟
We're fine!
نحن بخير
We're not hurt at all!
لم نتأذَ على الإطلاق
It's just the mirror that broke. We're safe in this dimension!
المرآة فقط تحطمت ولسنا نحن أنفسنا من تحطمنا
So you're okay!
أنتما بخير إذًا
I don't know what you're talking about, but that's good.
لم أفهم بالضبط ولكن هذا جيد
Luffy! Listen...
اسمع يا لوفي
Whatever. Let's start with this blabbermouth.
انسَ الأمر، لنبدأ بالغبي الثرثار
W-What are you gonna do to me?!
ما-ماذا ستفعل بي؟
Mama said I can kill you.
قالت إنها لا تبالي إن قتلتك
Th-Think about it!
فـ-فكر بالأمر
I'm your stepfather, Cracker-kun !
أنا زوج والدتك يا كراكر-كن
You used to be! Not anymore!
لقد كنتَ كذلك في السابق، ولكن ليس الآن
Mama considers her 43 ex-husbands as strangers,
تعد ماما أزواجها الـ43 غرباء لا رابطة بيننا وبينهم بالدم
How dare you!
لا يُعقَل
But I'm definitely related to my daughters by blood!
لكنني مرتبط بابنتاي بالدم بالتأكيد
Enough!
هذا يكفي
I just want to congratulate my daughter!
أريد فقط أن أبارك لابنتاي
Is this sympathy?
هل أشفقت عليه؟
After seeing someone dozens of times, they tend to grow on you!
قابلته كثير من المرات بالتأكيد أصبحت متعلقًا به
Th-Thank you!
شكرًا لك
This isn't good!
يا للمصيبة، استشعر خطرًا محدقًا
Minister Cracker is gonna start a fight here!
سيبدأ كراكر-ساما قتالًا هنا
Homies! Catch those two so we can finish this!
أيها الهوميز، أمسكوا بهذين الاثنين ولننتهي من الأمر
It's not safe here! Let's run!
المكان ليس آمنًا هنا، لنهرب
Hurry up!
أسرع
We'll take care of them!
سنتولى أمرهما هكذا
Don't let them get away!
لا تسمحوا لهما بالهرب
Hey, what's your name?!
أنت، ما اسمك؟
I'm Pound.
اسمي باوند
Did you mention Lola before?
هل ذكرتِ لولا سابقًا؟
Yeah.
نعم
Hang on a second...
انتظر للحظة
Found it!
ها هي ذي
What's that?
...إن هذه
It's the vivre card of my friend Lola's mom.
هذه الفيفر كارد الخاصة بـ والدة لولا
But I don't know if it's Big Mom's or not...
لكنني لا أعلم إن كانت لبيغ مام أو لا
What are you doing?! What's wrong, guys?!
ماذا تفعلون؟ ما الخطب أيها الرفاق؟
What's wrong, Kingbaum?! Even you're stopping?!
ما شأنك يا كينغبوم؟ حتى أنت توقفت؟
We can't do it, Brûlée!
لا يمكننا فعلها يا بروليه
We homies cannot fight against her!
لا يمكننا نحن الهوميز قتالها-جو
Wha...? Why not?!
لِمَ لا؟
I can sense Mama's powerful soul!
أشعر بروح ماما القوية-جو
No way...! Is this really... Big Mom's vivre card?!
أهذه حقًا الفيفر كارد الخاصة بـ بيغ مام؟
Luffy! No way.
أهذا لوفي؟ مستحيل
Are you okay?
يا هذا
C-Cracker-kun !
كـ-كراكر-كن
He has more than two arms!
ذراعيه تتزايد
Damn!
سحقًا
That bastard!
ذلك الوغد
I'm Biscuit Knight Cracker, one of the Three Sweet Commanders.
أنا فارس البسكويت كراكر، أحد جنرالات الحلوى الثلاث
Also known as...
وأُعرَف بلقب آخر
"Thousand Arms" Cracker.
كراكر ذو الألف ذراع
If I tap my arm once, it turns into two.
إن قرعتها مرة، تصبح اثنتان
If I do it again...
إن قرعتُها ثانيةً
it turns into three.
تصبح ثلاثة
They'll keep multiplying.
ستستمر بالتضاعف
His legs have multiplied, too.
تضاعفت قدماه أيضًا
Don't even dream about defeating me.
لا تحلم بهزيمتي حتى
I won't let you interfere with Mama's tea party!
لن أدعكَ تفسد حفلة شاي ماما
You've got extra limbs. So what?!
وماذا لو ازدادت أطرافك؟
Gear Second!
غير سكند
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Jet...
جيت
Bullet!
بوليت
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Hawk Whip!
هوك ويب
Luffy! No! Don't make this a serious fight! That isn't our goal here!
كلا يا لوفي، لا تستخدم قوتك بالكامل فهذا ليس هدفنا
We need to get out of here to get Sanji-kun back!
لنسرع بمغادرة المكان لاستعادة سانجي-كن
I make every fight serious...
لا أعرف إلا أن أقاتل
I don't know any other way!
!بكل قوتي
Charlotte Cracker (10th Son) One of the Three Sweet Commanders of the Big Mom Pirates and the Minister of Biscuit
شارلوت كراكر، الابن العاشر أحد جنرالات الحلوى الثلاثة، ووزير البسكويت - من قراصنة البيغ مام
Kingbaum Master of the Seducing Woods
كينغبوم، سيد غابة الإغواء
"Thousand Arms" Cracker One of the Three Sweet Commanders of the Big Mom Pirates Bounty: 860 Million Belly
كراكر ذو الألف ذراع، أحد جنرالات الحلوى الثلاثة من قراصنة بيغ مام - المكافأة: 860 مليون بيري